Farewell, Earth
The ship that is departing is
The Space Battleship
Yamato
It departs now to Iscandar,
at the end of the cosmos,
bearing its fate.
"We will come back, no matter what it takes"
Answer with a smile to the waving people
Going far from the Galaxy towards Iscandar
A faint gleam of hope
The Space Battleship Yamato
Episode 7
Farewell to the Solar System
Know that I'll return.
A bright red scarf.
On that day, come meet me once again.
For now, I dream amongst the stars,
at the end of the universe.
When he travels, a man's eyes should always be full of romance.
Safe Travels
A bright red scarf.
That girl was waving
A bright red scarf
Who do you think it was for?
Whoever it was
It doesn’t matter
Let each think it was for him
The hearts of men beginning a journey
Want a piece of romance
A bright red scarf